legacygames.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy / Legacy Games

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes Legacy Games, www.LegacyGames.com's, and Legacy Games Applications' (hereinafter, "Legacy Games" "we" or "us") current policies and practices with regard to Personal Information collected by us through the website www.LegacyGames.com (the "Site") and Applications. For additional information about our practices in the United States and Latin America regarding children's personal information, please read our Children's Privacy Policy.

Notification of Changes to This Policy

This policy was last updated on June 3, 2015.

Overview

At Legacy Games, protecting our user's privacy and security is a top priority. For this reason, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of your choices regarding the use of your personal information online. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, under what circumstances we disclose it to third-parties, and your rights to update or correct it. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law, and the changing nature of technology, Legacy Games' data collection and retention practices will change from time to time. Accordingly, we encourage you to check this page frequently. If material changes are made, we will notify you at this site and will not make new use of your previous collected data without your explicit consent.

Scope of Policy

This policy applies to Legacy Games. It does not apply to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link. You should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information.

Personal Information Collected

Other than cookies, as described below, the only Personal Information Legacy Games currently collects through its Site and Applications is the information you voluntarily give us when you use the Site, Applications and related services.

For example, you may use the Site to contact Legacy Games with questions and comments. When you fill out a form on the Site, you may provide your name and other contact information, including your name, your e-mail address, and your mailing address or other Personal Information. You are providing any and all such information voluntarily. If you would like to purchase a product or service offered via the Site and/or Applications, we will require only your name and your current, valid e-mail address. When you submit information to us through www.LegacyGames.com, you may receive a confirmation e-mail if you enter a valid e-mail address. When you use our Site to search for information, you are not providing us with any Personal Information. We offer the search features as a service to you. Legacy Games does not collect or retain any identifying information about you when you use the search features of our Site.

Use of Personal Information Collected

Legacy Games uses the Personal Information and other information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Legacy Games and our affiliates may also use this information to help us improve the content and functionality of our Site and Applications, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services. Legacy Games may send you surveys or solicit your feedback. We use surveys to gauge user interest in new products and premiums we may offer. We will ask for your feedback on games and site features. We will use the information we gather to improve our site and provide a more meaningful experience for our users. We may also use the information to alert you to offers and products in which you have expressed an interest. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "unsubscribe" from receiving future communications. We will never share your information outside of Legacy Games without your explicit consent.

Anonymous Information Collected

In addition to the information you provide when you use the Site and Applications, Legacy Games may use technology to collect Anonymous Information about the use of our Site and Applications. We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. These statistics are very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use this type of data in aggregate-that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical "ratings" about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other affiliates. We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.

Cookies

We use a technology nicknamed "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. Cookies allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on our web site if you choose not to accept cookies, such as favorites. In addition, you will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes or contests. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site.

Third Party Advertiser Cookies

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and Clear Gif technology (aka 1x1 Pixel .gifs, Web bugs) to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. Legacy Games does not use or have access to this information.

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, you may visit the web site of the National Advertising Initiative ("NAI") to opt-out of all network-advertising cookies. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies. 

Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Legacy Games may share some or all of the Personal Information collected through the Site and Applications with our affiliates, who use this data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Both Legacy Games and our affiliates may share Personal Information collected through its websites and Applications with third-party vendors who act for or on behalf of Legacy Games or our affiliates (for example, companies that provide support services to us, including data processing services, or that help us market our products and services). These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose. In addition, there may be some other, limited circumstances in which Legacy Games or our affiliates may share or transfer the Personal Information in our databases, for example, to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, or similar event.

Typically, to purchase and deliver products or services via the Site, Legacy Games will require that you provide your accurate name and email address. To the extent that Legacy requires that you provide your name and email address we will maintain that information to communicate with you and confirm delivery of your order and we will also maintain that information to comply with any legal obligations or for the administration of justice.

While no method of data transmission is guaranteed against unlawful third party interception or other misuse, Legacy Games uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure protection of your data including industry-standard encryption and offline security methods in our physical facilities.

Children

The Site is directed to Parents and the Applications are directed to Parents to play and learn in conjunction with their Children. Accordingly, any Personal Information collected would be presumed from a Parent. If at anytime we knowingly collect Personal Information from Children, we will request from the child an email address for their Parent and we will send via email a notice of our information practices and if necessary will require the Parent to affirmatively respond to the notice.

Link to Other Sites

This privacy policy applies only to Legacy Games' website at www.LegacyGames.com and Applications. Legacy Games and our affiliates may operate other websites and applications for different purposes and in different countries where different laws may apply. If you visit any Legacy Games website or Application, including www.LegacyGames.com, please take a moment to review the privacy policy posted on that site or application to learn what Personal Information may be collected through that website or application and how it is processed.

The Site and Applications may contain hyperlinks to websites and applications that are not operated by Legacy Games or our affiliates. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party websites or any association with their operators. Legacy Games does not control these websites and applications and is not responsible for their data practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any website or application you visit before using the website or application and providing any Personal Information about yourself.

Governing Law

This privacy policy forms part of our Site and Applications Terms and Conditions of use and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California without regard to conflict of law provisions. Any and all claims, causes of action or disputes (regardless of theory) arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, or the relationship between you and Legacy Games shall be brought exclusively in the courts located in the county of Los Angeles, California or the U.S. District Court for the Central District of California. You and Legacy Games agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located within the county of Los Angeles, California or the Central District of California, and agree to waive any and all objections to the exercise of jurisdiction over the parties by such courts and to venue in such courts.

Notice to California Residents

Under California civil code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the address written below.

Legacy Games  
1933 S. Broadway  
Suite 1162  
Los Angeles, CA 90007

Definitions

**Anonymous Information**. Anonymous information means information that does not directly or indirectly identify, and cannot reasonably be used to identify, an individual guest.

**Applications**. Applications means programs or services operated by us (or on our behalf) that may be displayed on various online, mobile or other platforms and environments, including those operated by third parties, which permits us to interact directly with our guests.

**Children**. Children means individuals who we have identified are not of legal age to consent to the collection and processing of their Personal Information. In the United States and Latin America, the term "children" refers to individuals under 13 years of age.

**Notice**. Notice may be by email to you at the last email address you provided us, by posting notice of such changes on our sites and applications, or by other means, consistent with applicable law.

**Parents**. Parents mean a parent or legal guardian.

**Personal Information**. Personal Information means information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) a particular individual, such as the individual's name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number. When Anonymous Information is directly or indirectly associated with Personal Information, this anonymous information also is treated as Personal Information.

Questions About Our Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or concerns about the way Legacy Games processes your personal data, please email us at customerservice@legacygames.com or mail us at:

Legacy Games  
1933 S. Broadway  
Suite 1162  
Los Angeles, CA 90007
